Mingyao, the Fu family has many rules
Sometimes you must learn to restrain your temper
Don't act like you did in the Su family
Making a scene online
Decency is important
But decency shouldn't be built on
Silencing those who were wronged
Mingyao is right
The Fu family's decency doesn't mean
Silencing family members when they are wronged
Defending oneself with evidence
The Fu family shouldn't feel ashamed
Those who should reflect are the ones who force them
To the point of needing evidence
Hmm
Tomorrow morning
The Fu Group will hold an
Internal project pre-review meeting
Chen Zhou will sit in
Mingyao will join too
Chairman, Mingyao just joined the Fu family
And she's already attending internal project meetings
Isn't it too soon
She's just sitting in
Since Mrs. Fu values evidence so much
Tomorrow is a good time to see the Fu Group's
Project complexity
Okay